

Portfolio click here

UX/UI Design

Certified UX/UI designer experienced in conducting UX research and UI design including wireframing & building prototypes for both mobile & web, as well as front-end web development.

Prototype Sample #1 (click here) • Prototype Sample #2 (click here) • Prototype Sample #3 (click here)

Work Experience

Senior Graphic Designer & Marketing Specialist

Navitas Credit Corp. Ponte Vedra, FL September 2012 — Present

Email Marketing

- Design and code all corporate email campaigns incorporating inline CSS, responsive and flat design, limited animation, and proper use of web fonts for best results in all generations of email clients, web browsers, mobile devices, and operating systems.
- Manage all email campaigns, using service provider Pardot for uploading and testing html
 files, importing distribution lists from Salesforce, building list segments including A/B testing,
 scheduling email drops such as drip campaigns, and reporting results of the email blasts.

Email Sample #1 (click here) • Email Sample #2 (click here) • Email Sample #3 (click here)

Website Design

- Designed responsive websites that resizes for all screens including mobile devices, incorporating
 corporate brand, best usability practices, prominent lead generation channels, and clear delivery
 of Navitas products & services. Websites built with HTML, CSS, and Javascript.
- Collaborated with software engineer to design wireframes and prototypess for an e-commerce, online community, and lead generation website.
- Designed vendor landing pages combining both Navitas and partner brands with multiple call-to-action links that convert visitors to new sales leads.

Website Sample #1 (click here) • Website Sample #2 (click here)

Corporate Identity

- Led entire rebranding including name change, logo designs, websites, signage, and collateral for corporation and all 6 business divisions.
- Designed trade show booths including 10' backdrop, podium stand, table covers, and signage.
 Responsible for pre-flighting and delivery of all booth artwork for best compliance with production specifications.
- Art Director for both Navitas and Equipment Street brand including logos, digital brochure, business cards, rate cards, credit applications, letterhead, and document templates.
- Wrote internal style guidelines for use of new logo and digital templates.

701 Market Street Unit 202 St. Augustine, FL 32095 904.347.7339, tel.



Page 2

Art Director

SQE, Inc. Orange Park, FL February 2007 – July 2012

- Lead designer for corporate identity such as logos, collateral, media kits, conference brochures, training catalogs, advertisements, presentations, and booth exhibits for five conferences per year with +2000 attendees.
- Responsible for front-end design, usability, and html/CSS coding of corporate websites, eNewsletters and direct email campaigns.
- Redesigned eNewsletters to increase ad revenue, subscriptions, and click-through rates. Resulted in a 20% jump in ad sales.
- Managed production schedule for creative staff, encompassing +250 deliverables per year to ensure all products were completed on time and within budget.
- Liaison to all print, web and mail house vendors for the magazine, conference and sales brochures, business cards, and all other collateral.
- Participated in creative meetings, heads-and-decks with editorial staff, and brainstorming with our marketing team. Created, wrote, and pitched ad campaigns to executive staff.
- Worked with the Vice President of Publishing on annual and quarterly budgets for creative department.

Better Software magazine

February 2007 – July 2016

- Art director for Better Software magazine a monthly 4-color, 56-page magazine with a print run of 50,000.
- Led the redesign of both the print and digital editions. Digital redesign improved visibility of type, reader engagement, maximized use of screen space on mobile devices, and created new advertising channels.
- Incorporated linked InCopy files to the InDesign template to streamline collaboration between the design and editorial teams and to increase productivity.
- Won three Charlie awards from the Florida Magazine Association for Best Cover design, Best Feature Design, and Best Special Theme or Show Issue.

Sales Director & Web Designer

Willis + Company, Inc. Key West & St. Augustine, FL June 2005 – January 2007

- Account management duties include new business development, client consultations, copy writing, storyboarding and pitching campaigns, vendor coordination, and ongoing client relations.
- Marketing efforts include advertising, writing and submitting press releases, conducting sales
 presentations, running trade show booths, direct email campaigns, social media outreach,
 professional networking, and community service.
- Art direction of logo and collateral, signage, websites, catalogs, advertisements, and booth exhibits that resulted in high value solutions for clients at affordable prices.
- Designed and built client websites generally for the tourism industry. Samples available in online portfolio.

701 Market Street Unit 202 St. Augustine, FL 32095 904.347.7339, tel.



Page 3

Senior Graphic Designer

IFES Washington, DC April 2001 - May 2005

Corporate Identity

- Led synchronized launch of new corporate identity within a 3-month period both at headquarters
 and for 23 field offices worldwide. Efforts included focus group meetings, storyboarding and
 pitching campaigns, organizational style guidelines, staff training, and presentations to the Board
 of Directors. Received leadership award with bonus and a promotion for my efforts.
- Designed collateral materials including new logo and slogan, letterhead and business cards in +4 languages, annual report, folders, brochures, and program guides using 2-color design for more cost effective printing.
- Art Director of democracy at large and its predecessor Elections Today, a 5-color,
 32-page quarterly magazine which features international democracy news.
- Publications include buyer's guide, international law compendiums, voter education posters, certified poll worker forms, election ballots in various languages and alphabets, and white papers for the organization.
- Experience designing in the following mediums raised acrylic and brushed steel for signage, engraving, watermarking (paper), silk screening, embroidery, embossing (paper and leather), die cutting, dull and gloss varnishes, spot colors, use of artisanal papers, foil stamping and encased enamel.
- Supported the Vice President of Communications and managed creative services staff with department work flow, staff training and mentoring, annual reviews, and art direction.
- Designed and managed organization's websites including www.IFES.org and www.ElectionGuide.org.

Portfolio

Click Here

Education

University of Central Florida UX/UI Bootcamp Certification University of Baltimore, graduate coursework, MA Publication Design Ohio University, Bachelor of Arts, Political Science

Computer Skills

Adept in both Macintosh and PC platforms: GitHub, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Figma, Visual Studio Code; Adobe Creative Cloud (XD, InDesign, InCopy, Illustrator, Photoshop, Acrobat, Dreamweaver, Animate); Salesforce, Pardot, Act-on, and Microsoft Office.

References

Available upon request

701 Market Street Unit 202 St. Augustine, FL 32095 904.347.7339, tel.